la-z-boy.com 2018-10-28

# Security & Privacy

##  POLICIES 

  *  Return Policy 
  *  Security & Privacy 
  *  Conflict Minerals Policy 
  *  CTSCA 

By visiting [La‑Z‑Boy.com](http://www.la-z-boy.com/), you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. This Policy is subject to change without notice and you should revisit this site frequently for the most current version of our policy.

## Our Pledge to You, Our Customer

La‑Z‑Boy respects your privacy. We do not sell, rent, loan or transfer any personal information regarding our customers to any unrelated third parties. Any information you give us about yourself is held with the utmost care and security and will not be used in ways to which you have not consented. Information collected on our Web site is used by La‑Z‑Boy Incorporated, its subsidiaries, affiliates and authorized agents (referred to collectively as “La‑Z‑Boy”) for La‑Z‑Boy purposes. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. La‑Z‑Boy will not collect any personal information about you except when specifically and knowingly provided by you. Examples of personally identifiable information include full name, home address, e-mail address and phone number. La‑Z‑Boy does automatically collect and analyze certain information from consumers, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; browser type, version, and time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system, and platform; purchase history, the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number; and products you viewed or searched for. La‑Z‑Boy will use reasonable efforts to include accurate and up-to-date information on this site. All users agree that all access to and use of this site and its content is at your own risk. La‑Z‑Boy will not be liable for any damage arising out of your access to, use of, or inability to use this site, or any errors or omissions in the content thereof. The materials in this site are provided without warranties of any kind, either expressed or implied.

You may choose to provide us with access to certain personal information stored by third parties through social media sites (such as Facebook and Twitter). The information we have access to varies by site and is controlled by your privacy settings on that site and your authorization. By authorizing La‑Z‑Boy to have access to this information, you agree that La‑Z‑Boy may collect, store and use this information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming any orders placed through our Web site. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.

## Use of Your Information

Authorized La‑Z‑Boy employees internally use information collected on our Web site for four main purposes. First, we collect information to figure out how to improve our site by seeing which areas' features and products are most popular. Second, we collect information to administer our business, provide superior service, and communicate information about our products and services that we believe to be of interest to you. Third, we collect information in order to personalize the site for our customers. For example, in the future, we may recommend products or features you may like based on what you have liked in the past. Last, we collect information to enable customers to participate in sweepstakes, contests and other activities on our Web site. If we collect any such information, we will only collect enough information to enable you to participate in the activity and no more. If we want to collect information for other purposes, we will inform you when we collect the information. Occasionally, La‑Z‑Boy may also share non-personal, summary information regarding our customers with unrelated third parties (for example, we publicly disclose the aggregate number of registered users of our Web site). However, La‑Z‑Boy does not share any personal information about any particular customer with unrelated third parties. (We may do so in the unlikely event that we believe that disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (i) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (ii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (iii) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of La‑Z‑Boy, its users or the public). If you do not want to receive e-mail from us and currently do, please reply to an e-mail that we have sent to you and insert "unsubscribe" in the subject line, or click the "Unsubscribe" link at the bottom of any of our emails.

La‑Z‑Boy also uses Adobe's analytics service, which uses cookies and web beacons to help us understand more about how our website is used, so that we can continue to improve it. To learn more, go to <http://www.adobe.com/content/dotcom/en/privacy/analytics.html>. To learn how to opt out, go to <http://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html#4>.

We do not knowingly collect or use personal information from children under 13, or equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction, without verifiable parental consent. If we learn that we have collected the personal information of a child under 13, or equivalent minimum age depending on jurisdiction, without first receiving verifiable parental consent, we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible.

Please contact us at the address below for any additional questions about the management or use of personal data.

## Use of Our Information

All of the writing on our site is the property of La‑Z‑Boy and is protected by copyright. None of the material may be reproduced without our written permission, with the exception of downloading or printing a single copy for your offline viewing. Many of the furniture products displayed throughout the pages of this Web site are protected by design patents issued by the United States. These design patents, which are owned by La‑Z‑Boy, cover one or more of the ornamental or aesthetic features forming the overall furniture product. Design patents may also be pending in the United States and other countries worldwide, which will serve to protect the designs of these furniture products when they are issued by the respective country. These furniture designs are exclusive property of La‑Z‑Boy and may not be copied, modified, or imitated without the prior written permission of La‑Z‑Boy. Additionally, many of the furniture products displayed throughout the pages of this Web site are protected by utility patents issued by the U.S. Patent and Trademark Office and patent offices in other countries. These utility patents, which are also owned by La‑Z‑Boy, cover one or more of the functional features or components of the furniture product, and/or its method of manufacture. Utility patents may also be pending in the United States and other countries which when issued by the respective country will serve to protect a functional feature or manufacturing method. We are certain you understand that La‑Z‑Boy must protect its intellectual property, including its patents, trademarks, and copyrights. Therefore, no license to La‑Z‑Boy's intellectual property has been granted by this Internet site.

## Cookies

La‑Z‑Boy uses a feature of your Internet Web browser called a "cookie" to assign a unique identification to your computer. Cookies are files that your Web browser places on your computer's hard drive. We use these cookie files to track your clicks as you go through the La‑Z‑Boy Web site, to tell us whether you have visited La‑Z‑Boy previously, and to help us determine whether you came to La‑Z‑Boy from a particular Internet link or banner advertisement. La‑Z‑Boy does not and cannot use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer. The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, you will not be able to use some La‑Z‑Boy.com features if you do not use cookies.

## Maintenance of Accurate Information

Procedures have been established to ensure that our product and promotional information is current and accurate in keeping with reasonable standards. We are committed to respond to requests to correct inaccurate information in a timely manner. Store prices may vary from prices shown here.

## Third-Party Sites

Our site contains links to other sites whose information practices and privacy policy may be different from our own. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

## Questions and Comments

We regularly review our compliance with this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or La‑Z‑Boy’s treatment of personal information, or if you see anything on our Web site that you feel is inappropriate, please contact us by [clicking here](mailto:webmaster@la-z-boy.com) or at:

**La‑Z‑Boy Incorporated**  
One La‑Z‑Boy Drive  
Monroe, MI 48162

When we receive formal written complaints at this address, it is our policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with any appropriate regulatory authorities in resolving any complaints that cannot be resolved between La‑Z‑Boy and you.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes). Each version of this Privacy Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date, and we will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.
